http://www.grafoplast.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy | Grafoplast Wiremarkers Inc.
This privacy statement is provided by Grafoplast Wiremarkers Inc (referred to as "us", "our", or "we" in these terms) for the information of visitors (referred to as "you" or "your" in these terms) to our website.
Grafoplast Wiremarkers Inc is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. This privacy statement explains how we use the information we collect about you and how you can instruct us if you prefer to limit the use of that information. In these terms, "third parties" means persons, firms or companies which are not subsidiary or associated or joint venture companies of Grafoplast Wiremarkers Inc. By using our website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Information gathered by us
The information that you provide enables us to supply you with further information about our company, products, services and any online marketing promotions. It also helps us to contact you if you have requested further information or logged an enquiry.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.We may on occasion, collect additional personal information from online marketing promotions or competitions which you enter through the website.
We may also use aggregated information and statistics for the purposes of monitoring website usage and our services and we may also provide such aggregated information to third parties. You cannot be personally identified by aggregated information.
As all of our ecommerce payments are processed via secure third party merchants (such as PayPal & SecurePay), we do not access or store any credit information directly. Our merchant service may share certain personal information such as your name, contact details or shipping/billing address to enable your transaction to occur. For more information, please check the PayPal or SecurePay privacy policy.
Cookies
You may be aware that there is a technology called "cookies". This is a file that is transferred from the website to the hard drive of your computer. We may use cookies to track your activities on our website. A cookie will not allow a website operator to obtain information of a personal nature that will identify you to us, such as your name and address. We will only be aware of such information if you provide the information to us or you have set the preferences in your browser to provide this information automatically.
Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users.
Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to track information on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.
We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.
Opting out:
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser add on.
At Grafoplast Wiremarkers Inc we only want to communicate with you if you want to hear from us. In the case of direct marketing you are able to "unsubscribe" at any time, for any reason. Unsubscribing means that you would like to be removed from all of our mailing lists. You can do so online or by contacting us on the details below, or via this link.
Postal Address
Attention: Customer Service Manager
Grafoplast Wiremarkers Inc
6875 E. 48th Ave
Denver, Colorado 80216 USA
WE DEAL DIRECT
-
WE DELIVER NEXT DAY
© 2020 Grafoplast Wiremarkers Inc.
